Usa-chan?
うさっちゃん?
Isn't it Usa-chan?
うさっちゃんじゃないですか?
Pyon!
ぴょん!
cute!
かわいい!
Yes, yes!
そうそう そう!
Ah ~ amazing!
あ 〜すごい!
Do you like cosplay?
コスプレとか好きなの?
I can't believe it's that, haven't you ever been to an event?
まさかあれだよね、イベントとかに出たことないよね?
Especially not.
ましてないですね
Back, slowly.
後ろ、ゆっくり
Ah, yes, yes!
あ〜そうそうそう!
Nice~ Is it okay to have an erotic girl?
いいね〜 エロいうさっちゃんがいていいのか?
Do your ears fall off easily?
耳がすぐ落ちちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's like sitting tight like I am now.
ちょっと、今みたいにキュッと座っちゃうようなもの
Ah, yes, yes!
あ〜そうそうそう!
Oh wow!
お〜すごい!
amazing!
すごい!
Oh, what is that?
あ、なにそれ?
You can see everything!
まる見えじゃん!
not at all.
全然
You can see it all!
まる見えじゃん、それ!
Ah, I think I can do it!
あ〜いけそう!
a
あ
~ Looks good!
〜 いけそう!
a!
あ!
a
あ
~ Looks good!
〜 いけそう!
Ah, I think I can do it!
あ〜いけそう!
love
あ 〜 い
Ke so!
け そう!
It came out a lot.
めっちゃ出ちゃったよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you excited about cosplay?
コスプレ、興奮しちゃった?
Ehehe!
え へへ!
I forgot.
忘れちゃったよ
Not at all, or should I say, it's just my skin.
全然なって、言うかその、肌っけっけ
Yes, yes!
そうそうそう!
Wow!
うわ!
This is nice.
これいいな
I wish I could say this much.
これで、こんなにいってもらえばよかった
Next time, next time.
今度、今度して